https://carshopinc.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

My Car Shop My Wish List
Checkout Sign In
All Parts - - Fasteners - - Oils, Fluids and Sealer - - Tools - - Books Videos and Software - - Drivetrain - - Chassis Components - - Exhaust - - Promotional Collectables and Apparel - - Exterior Components - - Towing Equipment - - Safety Equipment - - Gaskets and Seals - - Fittings Hoses and Valves - - Mobile Electronics - - Engines and Components - - Suspension and Components - - Gauges and Accessories - - Brakes - - Paints and Finishing - - Heating and Cooling - - Air and Fuel - - Steering and Components - - Interior and Accessories - - Ignitions and Electrical - - Wheels and Tires - - V8 Conversions - - Gift Cards - - Fastronix Solutions - - Engines and Components|Main - - Books Videos and Software|Main - - Oils - - Car Shop Tools - - Tools, Towing, Wheels & Tires Search Top Search:
ALLSTAR PERFORMANCE
brandmotion and 1>1
COMP CAMS
EDELBROCK
PROFORM
More++
Advanced ++
Parts CartMy Cart
All Parts
Air & Fuel, Brakes, Chassis
Air and FuelAir Cleaners, Filters, Intakes and ComponentsAir and Fuel Cooling Systems and ComponentsAluminum Fill CapCarburetors and ComponentsFuel Cells, Tanks and ComponentsFuel Injection Systems and Components - ElectronicFuel Injection Systems and Components - MechanicalFuel Pumps, Regulators and ComponentsIntake Manifolds and ComponentsOxygen Sensors, Controllers and ComponentsPerformance PackagesNitrous Oxide Systems and ComponentsSuperchargers, Turbochargers and ComponentsThrottle Cables, Linkages, Brackets and ComponentsBrakesBrake Cooling Kits and ComponentsBrake Systems And ComponentsEmergency-Parking Brakes and ComponentsLine LocksMaster Cylinders-Boosters and ComponentsWheel Hubs, Bearings and ComponentsChassis ComponentsBushings and MountsChassis Fabrication MaterialsChassis and Frame ComponentsCrossmembersRoll Cages
Drivetrain, Engine, Exhaust
DrivetrainAutomatic Transmissions and ComponentsBellhousings and ComponentsBelt and Chain DriveClutches and ComponentsDifferentials and Rear-End ComponentsDrive Shafts and Components4x4 Driveline ComponentsManual Transmissions and ComponentsQuick Change Differentials and ComponentsShifters and ComponentsEngines and ComponentsBelts and PulleysCamshafts and ValvetrainConnecting Rods and ComponentsCrankshafts and ComponentsCylinder Heads and ComponentsEngine BearingsEngines, Blocks and ComponentsEngine Covers, Pans and Dress-Up ComponentsEngine Pre Heaters and ComponentsHarmonic BalancersOiling SystemsPistons and Piston RingsCamshaftsExhaustCatalytic ConvertersExhaust Brakes and ComponentsExhaust Pipes, Systems and ComponentsHeaders, Manifolds and ComponentsHeat ProtectionMufflers and Resonators
Electrical, Interior, Mobile Electronics
Ignitions and ElectricalCharging SystemsComputers, Chips, Modules and ProgrammersData AcquisitionDelay Boxes and ComponentsDistributors, Magnetos and Crank TriggersElectric Fan Wiring and ComponentsIgnition ComponentsIgnition Boxes and ComponentsStartersWiring ComponentsWiring HarnessesInterior and AccessoriesCarpeting, Vinyl Flooring and Floor MatsDash AccessoriesDoor AccessoriesInterior Lights and ComponentsInterior TrimPedals and Pedal PadsRear View Mirrors and ComponentsSeats and ComponentsSound Deadening MaterialWindshield Sun ShadeMobile ElectronicsCell Phone ProtectorPower AccessoriesProximity WarningRace Radios and ComponentsTransponders and ComponentsVideo Accessories
Exterior, Fasteners, Fittings & Hoses
Exterior ComponentsBody Panels and ComponentsCar and Truck CoversDecals and MoldingsDeflectors and VisorsET Dial Boards and ComponentsGrillesLights and ComponentsMirrors, Side View and TowingRoof Racks and ComponentsRunning Boards, Truck Steps and ComponentsTruck Bed and Trunk ComponentsWeatherstripping and Rubber DetailsWindows and ComponentsWindshield Wipers and WashersFastenersBody Fastener KitsBrake Fastener KitsBulk FastenersComplete Sprint CarDrivetrain Fastener KitsEngine Fastener KitsFuel CellInterior FastenerRod Ends Clevises and ComponentsSteering Fastener KitsSuspension Fastener KitsWheel and Tire Fastener KitsFittings Hoses and ValvesClamps and BracketsFittings and PlugsHose, Line and TubingSilicone HoseValves
Gaskets, Gauges, Heating & Cooling
Gaskets and SealsBrake System GasketsDrivetrain Gaskets and SealsEngine Gaskets and SealsExterior GasketsGasket MaterialO-rings, Grommets and Vacuum CapsPower Steering Gaskets and SealsGauges and AccessoriesGauge ComponentsGauge KitsIndividual GaugesHeating and CoolingAir ConditioningDucts and AccessoriesFansFluid Cooler PumpsHeatersOverflow Tanks and Catch CansOil and Fluid CoolersRadiatorsThermostats, Housings and FillersWater Pumps
Oils, Sealers, Paints
Oils, Fluids and SealerCleaners and DegreasersFuelsFuel System AdditivesGreaseLubricants and PenetrantsOils, Fluids and AdditivesSealers, Gasket Makers and GluesTire Softeners and TreatmentsPaints and FinishingPaints, Coatings and MarkersWaxes, Polishes and Protectants
Safety, Steering, Suspension
Safety EquipmentDriver CoolingFire ExtinguishersFresh Air SystemsHelmets and AccessoriesParachutes and ComponentsSafety ClothingSafety RestraintsShields and BlanketsWindow Nets and ComponentsSteering and ComponentsBushings and MountsPower Steering and ComponentsRack and Pinions, Steering Boxes and ComponentsSpindles, Ball Joints and ComponentsSteering Columns, Shafts and ComponentsSteering LinkageSteering Wheels and ComponentsSuspension and ComponentsAir Suspension and ComponentsBushings and MountsFront Suspension ComponentsRear Suspension ComponentsShocks, Struts, Coil-Overs and ComponentsSprings and ComponentsSuspension Limiters and ComponentsSuspension KitsSuspension Tubes and ComponentsSway Bars and Components
Tools, Towing, Wheels & Tires
ToolsAir Tanks and ToolsBrake Bleeders and AccessoriesCar Shop ToolsElectrical and Electrical Testing ToolsEngine-RelatedHand and Other ToolsShop EquipmentStorageSuspension TuningWheel and Tire ToolsTowing EquipmentHitchesTie-Down Straps and ComponentsTongue JacksTrailer CarpetTrailer Wiring and ElectronicsWinchesWheels and TiresTires and TubesTire and Wheel AccessoriesWheels
V8 Conversion Parts
V8 ConversionsLS Conversion PartsRanger V8 Conversion PartsS10 V8 Conversion Parts
More Categories
Categories
New Parts
Deals
About Us
Centrally located in Moline IL we have been serving the performance enthusiast for over 30 years.
We pride ourselves on excellent customer service.
Online since 1996 we have served 10's of thousands of customers online with the same excellent service that we give our local customers.
Backed by a centrally located 153,000 square footwarehouse with over 100,000 square feet devoted entirely to warehouse functions which include receiving, stocking, packing and shipping.
Nearly 22 linear miles of shelving provide adequate space to take maximum advantage of volume purchases, saving us money and allowing us to pass these savings on to you.
Whether you are a Street Car, Hot Rod, Drag Racing, Circle Track, Road Racing or Truck enthusiast we can supply the parts and supplies you need at reasonable prices and with prompt delivery.
Events
TBA
Brands
Contact Us
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
This privacy policy sets out how this website (hereafter "Car Shop Inc") uses and protects any information that you give the Store while using this website. The Store is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The Store may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this request using our Contact Us information.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect as well as Google Analytics Cookies, to opt out of Google Analytics see https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie Name
Cookie Description
_ga
Used to distinguish users.
_gid
Used to distinguish users.
_gat
Used to throttle request rate.
AMP_TOKEN
Contains a token that can be used to retrieve a Client ID from AMP Client ID service. Other possible values indicate opt-out, inflight request or an error retrieving a Client ID from AMP Client ID service.
_gac_*****
Contains campaign related information for the user. If you have linked your Google Analytics and Google Ads accounts, Google Ads website conversion tags will read this cookie unless you opt-out.
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
